As Prophet TB Joshua was giving an inspiring
message during the SCOAN Sunday live service
his spirit was quickly alerted that something
was about to happen in the congregation.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
MANIFESTATION OF EVIL SPIRITS
Who are you?
I am a strong man.
MANIFESTATION OF EVIL SPIRITS
I gave her sickness.
I destroyed her.
It is time, tell your neighbor - it is time.
Through her dreams,
from her mother's side.
Back on the floor.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
See your friend, she never knew
what brought her out, she is ashamed.
What are you doing there?
What happened?
You know, you wanted to fight me?
SET FREE IN JESUS' NAME
Oh God, thank you!
This is why the Bible says
the One from above is above all.
Amen!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Thank you, Jesus.
Do you know what happened to you?
No.
You slapped me,
let me show you where you slapped me. See.
Sorry, sir, sorry, prophet.
So you are free.
Thank you.
We will do every property to set you free.
Amen.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Thank you, Jesus, I am free.
I am delivered.
Thank you, Jesus.
TESTIMONY TIME
Hallelujah!
Thank you, Jesus
Thank you, Lord.
Thank you for planning and
preparing this wonderful day for me.
People of God, help me to praise this Lord.
Thank you, Jesus.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
My name is Maria, I'm from South Africa,
the man beside me is my husband.
It all started
from my childhood. I came from the family
of ancestry where they worship ancestors.
I grew up in my grandmothers
house where my aunt was a 'sangoma',
she initiated people. As a child, growing up
I used to do what they were doing,
to dance with them, do all those
kind of things they were doing.
As I was growing up like that,
I didn't like what they were doing as 'sangomas'.
Each and every year they used to cut us
and put the charms in our body
whatever that the sangomas were doing
we were also doing.
When they danced or drank those medicines,
we were drinking also with them.
I was part of them because when they
would come to seek for help from my aunt,
I would be the one helping my aunt bathing people,
cutting them. When she cut them
I'll would be following my aunt
to give her the medicine to cut that person.
I started dreaming and my dreams
would come to pass.
I dreamt about two snakes, with these two snakes -
I used to go to the river to talk with them.
They were like my friends because always I would
see myself there in the river talking to them.
They wanted me to be in the
water with them.
As I grew up, I started becoming very angry,
I didn't know where this anger was from.
Then I didn't have forgiveness in my heart.
I tried to come out of this things of 'sangoma' because
in my heart I didn't like what they were doing.
This 'sangoma' things - I didn't like it.
I went to this known big Church in South Africa.
Most of the people know this church.
When I went there, they prophesied to me -
they said I was a prophetess. Then I
started drinking all those instructions
that they were giving to me.
I started prophesying and my
prophecy was not the prophecy of...
I would say of God because it was always negative.
The prophecy would tell that someone would die
or you would lose your job. And that was true because
it happened mostly.
Sometimes it would come in dreams.
The owner of the church would
come to me and tell me that
such and such a person would come
and would be wearing such a clothes
and in which direction he would be sitting.
Then I would know, he would
tell me everything of that person.
Okay, you say they would come to you -
who would come to you in the dream to tell you this?
They owner of the church.
Okay, so you would see that evil spirit appear to you
in the dream. You mentioned before that
you were seeing these snakes.
Would these snakes continue to
appear to you at this point?
Yes, they would continue to
come to me speaking with me.
Okay, so these snakes would appear to you
and tell you that someone will be coming to the service,
give them a word of prophecy and the following day
when you went to that church
you would now see that same person
and give him a word of prophecy.
Yes, the outcome of these prophecies were not good.
Because when I dreamt of someone,
I would see that person dying,
or losing his job and it would happen the way
I told him, the way I saw it and it brought fear.
The people had fear,
and they didn't have peace.
Always they were afraid something
bad would happen because
of the prophecy from that place.
Can you explain how this affected
you in the area of your marriage,
your relationship with your husband?
It affected me because these dreams would come -
whatever step he would be taking
or something that was not good -
I would be seeing it before he knew that I knew it.
Then it would create anger to me
and I would be so angry with him. If I got angry,
something bad would happen to him. As he was self-employed,
in my heart I wished that
there would be no job
or people would not pay him - then
it would happen like that.
And I would be angry by then.
So when you were angry and you
thought or spoke evil
concerning your husband's business,
it would come to pass.
And what about your relationship
with him in terms of affection
or closeness as a husband and wife?
The affection sometimes was not there.
So could you explain to us, madam,
how did you now discover the
Synagogue, Church of All Nations
and come to receive your deliverance last week?
I discovered the television through my husband -
his friend told him about the television.
What was it you saw in Emmanuel TV
that really convicted you or touched you?
The prophecies of the man of God -
when he prophesies, he gives the solution.
Then I saw the teachings of the man
of God, when he reads the Bible,
I refer to the Bible. Then I learnt a lot that
God is alive and He is there and He delivers.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Glory be to God, so that's how you decided to come
to the Synagogue, Church of All Nations.
When the man of God arrived here,
I felt the fire, I was burning, I couldn't hold myself.
I wanted to grab him,
there was this force that was busy on me.
I don't know how to explain it even today.
After my deliverance, I felt ashamed.
I came back to my senses.
I didn't know what happened.
I saw just people looking at me,
then I felt ashamed.
God is awesome!
I feel peace in me, I don't have
those bad thoughts
in my mind - I feel peace.
I feel calm in my body.
And that dream seeing those
snakes appear to you -
everything has come to an end
after the deliverance?
I don't see anything of those, I sleep like a baby.
Amen, let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
We give glory to God for the wonderful
deliverance our sister received.
We believe you are really in a position
to advise people of God,
especially concerning the area that
satan was using you in the past
to give false, fake words of prophecy to people.
What do you want to advise people of God in the light
of this deliverance that you have received?
My advice especially to the Christians -
when you are a Christian,
don't play a Christian,
be a real Christian.
Don't be just a goer to church,
listen and obey what is there.
If you don't - when someone curses you,
if you don't have God,
that thing will come to pass.
People of God, Emmanuel! (God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Kaizer Mata.
This beautiful woman beside me is my wife.
We have been married for more
than 15 years now.
What she was talking about is true
because I know all these things.
The evil spirit in her made her
to be more angry all the time.
It did all sorts of things that were
not good in our marriage,
it scattered my business.
Whatever she said came to pass,
what she was saying is more than
what she's explaining now.
Remember, for 15 years I have
been staying with a woman
being forced by a spirit - an evil spirit.
So, a lot of things has happened.
I can't say much but what I would
like to thank the man of God for,
is that I'm very happy because the evil spirit has gone.
Since she was delivered on Sunday,
I was with her in the church.
Things that I couldn't see from her -
I could now begin to see from her.
She has totally changed.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
I don't even know what to say,
I can only say - thank you, Jesus.
Amen, lets put our hands together for Jesus Christ.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
So that peace, that love, that affection in the marriage
has been completely restored after the deliverance?
Yes!
Thank you, Jesus! Lets put our
hands together for Jesus Christ!
We thank God for you, sir.
And what is your own word of advice
to viewers all over the world, sir?
My word of advice to viewers all over
the world, even the people inside here -
Whenever you have got a situation like us,
run to God
because if you run to false churches,
you can lose your life.
But because God is there, we were inside that church,
we did not know that it was a false church -
we thought maybe it was a church.
We found out that it was not a real
church through Emmanuel TV.
in 2008. Then we started following Emmanuel TV
until to this date.
Amen, let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
TT: Lizz Ndung'u 05/09/2018
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 12/09/2018